Guide to the Brooklyn Heights Association Records BCMS.0035
Brooklyn Collection
- Committee Minutes – Smoke Nuisance, 1924 (Box 13)
- Committee Minutes – Traffic, 1923 (Box 13)
- Committee Minutes – Parks & Playgrounds, 1923-1926 (Box 13)
- Committee Reports – Interim, 1951 (Box 13)
- Committee Minutes – Zoning, 1923-1936, 1955 (Box 13)
- Communications to Members, 1960 (Box 13)
- Correspondence Miscellaneous, 1970-1977 (Box 13)
- Correspondence Miscellaneous, 1962-1965 (Box 13)
- Correspondence Miscellaneous, 1966-1969 (Box 13)
- A.B. Dick Office Equipment (Box 13)
- Duval Legacy, 1950 (Box 13)
- Montague Street Track Removal, 1924 (Box 13)
- Homosexuality, 1966-1972 (Box 13)
- Nominating Committee, 1925-1955 (Box 13)
- Planting Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 13)
- 38-40 Hicks Street Preservation, 1970 (Box 13)
- Helicopters, 1965 (Box 13)
- Playground, 1937-1953 (Box 13)
- Playground (Brooklyn Bridge Plot) Baseball Field, 1923 (Box 13)
- Playground /RE Hooper, 1922-1936 (Box 13)
- Housing Cadman Plaza, 1959-1960 (Box 13)
- Housing Cadman Plaza, 1961 (Box 13)
- Housing Cadman Plaza I, inlcudes photos, 1962 (Box 13)
- Housing Cadman Plaza II, 1962 (Box 13)
- Housing Cadman Plaza, 1963 (Box 13)
- Housing Cadman Plaza, 1964 (Box 13)
- Housing Cadman Plaza, 1965 (Box 13)
- Housing Cadman Plaza, 1967 (Box 13)
- Housing/ North End, 1963-1965 (Box 13)
- Housing Low Income, Atlantic Avenue, 1961 (Box 13)
- Housing Violation Committee, 1959-1961 (Box 13)
- Housing/North End, 1966-1969 (Box 13)
- Housing Committee, 1952-1955 (Box 14)
- Housing Committe, 1956 (Box 14)
- Housing Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
- Annual report of the Department of Police and Excise of the city of Brooklyn, 1959 (Box 14)
- Housing Violations, 1968 (Box 14)
- Legal Fees, 1968 (Box 14)
- Housing Violations, 1968 (Box 14)
- Legal Fees, 1938-1940 (Box 14)
- News Clippings – Annual & Board Meetings, circa 1931 (Box 14)
- Membership Campaign, 1947-1951 (Box 14)
- Membership Campaign, 1960 (Box 14)
- Membership Committee, 1956-1577 (Box 14)
- Membership Committee, 1955 (Box 14)
- Membership Correspondence, 1923-1950 (Box 14)
- Minutes of Board of Governors (Not in Minute Book), 1935-1937 (Box 14)
- Movie Theaters Henry and Orange Street, 1970 (Box 14)
- Neighborhood Issues, 1975 (Box 14)
- News Clippings – Cleanliness and Smoke, 1930 (Box 14)
- News Clippings - Liquor and Café Licenses, 1944 (Box 14)
- News Clippings – Houses and Housing, 1950 (Box 14)
- News Clippings – Noise (Box 14)
- News Clippings – Personal, 1941-1950 (Box 14)
- News Clippings – Police Protection and Crime, 1952 (Box 14)
- News Clippings – Traffic and Parking, 1932 (Box 14)
- News Clippings – Zoning and Waterfront (Box 14)
- Newsletters Monthly, 1930-1937 (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1964-1972 (Box 14)
- News Clippings – Public Improvements, 1935-1944 (Box 14)
- News Clippings – Zoning General, 1934 (Box 14)
- News Clippings – Historical, 1951 (Box 14)
- Mary Alicia Crowell (items missing from folder), 1958 (Box 14)
- Following folders formerly housed in binders (Box 14)
- BHA Minutes of Executive Committee and Board of Governors, Nov. 1922-Jan. 1935 (Box 14)
- BHA Minutes of Executive Committee and Board of Governors, Jan. 1935-Dec. 1945 (Box 14)
- BHA Minutes - Land Use Zeigelbaum, Fulton St., Hotels, Palmieri, Burger King, 1975-1979 (Box 14)
- BHA Minutes Land Use South Brooklyn Waterfront & Columbia Street, Fulton Ferry, Empire Stores, Block 207, 1976-1978 (Box 14)
- Minutes Board of Governors Meetings, 1973 (Box 14)
- Minutes Board of Governors Meetings, 1974 (Box 14)
- Minutes Board of Governors Meetings, 1974-1976 (Box 14)
- Minutes Board of Governors Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 14)
- BHA Montague Street (Correxpondence, Clippings, Reports), 1974-1979 (Box 14)
- BHA Zoning (Correxpondence, Clippings, Reports), 1974-1979 (Box 14)
- BQE – Clippings, Reports, Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 14)
- BQE – Clippings, Reports, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 14)
- Reports, By –Laws, Membership List, Miscellaneous Board Documents, 1966-1974 (Box 15)
- BHA Minutes of Board Meetings, 1971-1973 (Box 15)
- BHA Treasurer's Reports (Monthly Treasurer's, Annual Treasurer's, Playground Treasurer's), 1925-1953 (Box 15)
- BHA Minutes of Board of Governors, Jan. 1946-Dec. 1954 (Box 15)
- BHA Minutes of Annual Meetings, Nov. 1923-March 1952 (Box 15)
- BHA Minutes of Board of Governors, 1955-1957 (Box 15)
- BHA Minutes of Board of Governors, 1960-1966 (Box 15)
- Brooklyn Heights Association Bulletin, 1958-1960 (Box 15)
- Brooklyn Heights Association Bulletin, 1961-1966 (Box 15)
- Brooklyn Heights Association Bulletin, 1967-1970 (Box 15)
- Brooklyn Heights Association Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box 15)
- Brooklyn Heights Association Bulletin, 1973-1975 (Box 15)
- Brooklyn Heights Association Bulletin, 1976-1980 (Box 15)
- C.R.C Membership, 1989 (Box 15)
- Charter Revision, 1988 (Box 15)
- Charter Revision, 1989 (Box 15)
- C.R.C Landmarks Changes (Box 15)
- Roebling Project: NYSCA Grant Application (Box 16)
- Roebling Project: Sculpture Competition (Box 16)
- Roebling Project: Roebling Monument Competition, 1985 (Box 16)
- Roebling Project: Roebling Monument Project Art Advisory Group/Artists (Box 16)
- Roebling Project: Outline I (Box 16)
- Roebling Project: Outline II (Box 16)
- City Planning Commission "Zoning Resolution – Amendment" (Sensitive) (Box 16)
- N.Y.C. Department of City Planning "Waterfront Revitalization" (Sensitive) (Box 16)
- Sensitive Material *** Piers Development (Box 16)
- N.Y.C. Department of City Planning "Plan for the Brooklyn Waterfront" (Box 16)
- N.Y.C. Department of City Planning "Comprehensive Waterfront Plan" (Box 16)
- Brooklyn Heights Piers 1-6 (Box 16)
- Port Authority Plans for Brooklyn Piers 1-6 (Box 16)
- N.Y.C. Public Development Corporation/PDC (Box 16)
- Development and Beautification of Highways (Box 16)
- Joyce Curll – Piers Proposal Piers 1-9 (Box 16)
- BHA Piers Committee, 1986 (Box 16)
- BHA Brooklyn Piers Taskforce, 1987 (Box 16)
- BHA Brooklyn Piers Taskforce Meetings, 1986 (Box 16)
- BHA Piers Committee, 1988 (Box 16)
- BHA Piers Committee – Public Trust Doctrine (Box 16)
- BHA Piers Committee – Parks (Box 16)
- BHA Piers Committee - Sports Complex (Box 17)
- BHA Piers Committee – Marina (Box 17)
- BHA Piers Committee – Funding (Box 17)
- BHA Piers Committee - Land Trust (Box 17)
- BHA Piers Committee – Anti High Rise Buildings (Box 17)
- BHA Piers Committee – Cobble Hill Concerns (Box 17)
- Promenade Montague St. Entrance to Esplanade Proposed Redesign, 1982-1983 (Box 17)
- Promenade Montague St. Entrance to Esplanade Proposed Redesign, Jan.-July 1984 (Box 17)
- Promenade Montague St. Entrance to Esplanade Proposed Redesign, Aug.-Dec. 1984 (Box 17)
- Promenade Montague St. Entrance to Esplanade Proposed Redesign Maps and Plans (Box 17)
- Noise – In Land Use Planning (Box 17)
- Watchtower High Rise Proposal, 1988 (Box 17)
- Miscellaneous Proposals for Piers (Box 17)
- BHA Waterfront Committee – Scope of Services Report (Box 17)
- Piers 1-6 – Consultants I (Box 17)
- Piers 1-6 – Consultants II (Box 17)
- Piers 1-6 – Consultants III (Box 17)
- Piers 1-6 – Consultants IV (Box 17)
- Piers 1-6 – Proposals I (Box 17)
- Piers 1-6 – Proposals II (Box 17)
- Dept. of Environmental Protection – Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1985 (Box 17)
- Block 239 Community Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 17)
- Block 239 Community Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 17)
- Morgan Stanley Building – Local Paper Clippings (Box 17)
- Morgan Stanley Building – Neon Circles (Box 17)
- Morgan Stanley Safety Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 17)
- One Pierreppont Plaza– Parking (Box 17)
- Brooklyn Heights Building Elevations (Box 17)
- St. Ann's School v. Forest City Ratner Litigation (Box 17)
- Forest City Pierrepont Term Sheet & Environmental Impact Statement (Box 17)
- Redevelopment of Piers 1-6, Community Boards 2 and 6, 1986-1988 (Box 18)
- Watchtower Re-Zoning (See Box #30) (Box 18)
- Watchtower Board of Estimates (Box 18)
- Watchtower – Letter to Board of Estimates Re: Zoning Change and Watchtower I (Box 18)
- Watchtower – Letter to Board of Estimates Re: Zoning Change and Watchtower II (Box 18)
- Watchtower – Urban Design Impact Analysis (Box 18)
- Watchtower – Final Environmental Impact Statement (Box 18)
- Watchtower – Final Environmental Impact Statement – Urban Design Impact Analysis (Box 18)
- Petition to the Board of Estimate I (Box 19)
- Petition to the Board of Estimate II (Box 19)
- BHA Statement in opposition to Zoning Map Change and Related Construction Proposed by Watchtower Society (Box 19)
- Watchtower News Articles (Box 19)
- Court Street Taskforce (Box 19)
- 85 Jay Street – Land Use Review Application (Box 19)
- 85 Jay Street Re-Zoning – Environmental Assessment Statement (Box 19)
- Proposed Rezoning of Blocks 208 and 204 (Box 19)
- Community Board No. 2 – Piers Subcommittee (Box 19)
- BHA Committee on the Redevelopment of the Brooklyn Heights Pier I, 1986 (Box 20)
- BHA Committee on the Redevelopment of the Brooklyn Heights Piers II, 1986 (Box 20)
- BHA Committee on the Redevelopment of the Brooklyn Heights Piers I, 1987 (Box 20)
- BHA Committee on the Redevelopment of the Brooklyn Heights Piers II, 1987 (Box 20)
- BHA Committee on the Redevelopment of the Brooklyn Heights Piers, 1988 (Box 20)
- BHA Committee on the Redevelopment of Piers 1-6 Press Releases (Box 20)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 1 12/10/84-8/28/86 I (Box 21)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 1 12/10/84-8/28/86 II (Box 21)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 1 12/10/84-8/28/86 III (Box 21)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 2 9/2/86-11/17/86 I (Box 21)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 2 9/2/86-11/17/86 II (Box 21)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 2 9/2/86-11/17/86 III (Box 21)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 3 11/19/86-2/26/87 I (Box 21)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 3 11/19/86-2/26/87 II (Box 21)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 3 11/19/86-2/26/87 III (Box 22)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 4 3/2/87-7/22/87 I (Box 22)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 4 3/2/87-7/22/87 II (Box 22)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 4 3/2/87-7/22/87 III (Box 22)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 5 7/24/87-11/19/87 I (Box 22)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 5 7/24/87-11/19/87 II (Box 22)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 5 7/24/87-11/19/87 III (Box 22)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 6 11/24/87-4/29/88 I (Box 23)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 6 11/24/87-4/29/88 II (Box 23)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 6 11/24/87-4/29/88 III (Box 23)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 7 5/1/88-11/10/88 I (Box 23)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 7 5/1/88-11/10/88 II (Box 23)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 7 5/1/88-11/10/88 III (Box 23)
- Piers 1-6 Vol. 8 11/11/88-11/28/88 (Box 23)
- Piers 1-6 « Brooklyn Waterfront Public or Private Use (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 Lists and Labels (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 BHA Lists: Piers and Politicos (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 Watchtower comments on proposed re-zoning (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 Port Authority Report & List of Commissioners (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 Community Board #2 Misc I (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 Community Board #2 Misc II (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 Community Board #2 Minutes of Subcommittee Meetings (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 Krogius Correspondence (Australia) (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 Checks Received by BHA (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 BHA Prints & Bills (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 City Council Panel on Waterfront Development (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 National Endowment for the Arts Application Forms (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 BHA Lobbying Committee (Box 24)
- Piers 1-6 Development Reports (Box 25)
- Piers 1-6 Miscellaneous Reports (Box 25)
- Piers 1-6 Urban Planner Resume and Plan Draft (Box 25)
- Piers 1-6 BHA Redevelopment Committee (Box 25)
- Piers 1-6 Original Donor Lists (Box 25)
- Piers 1-6 BHA Statement on Redevelopment of Piers (Box 25)
- Piers 1-6 Harbor Park (Box 25)
- Piers 1-6 BHA Future of the Piers (Box 25)
- Piers 1-6 BHA & Community Presentations I (Box 25)
- Piers 1-6 BHA & Community Presentations II (Box 25)
- Piers 1-6 BHA & Community Presentations III (Box 25)
- Piers 1-6 Harbor Park Coalition Tentative Agenda (Box 25)
- Piers 1-6, Redistricting Lawsuit (Cravath Swaine & Moore Briefs) (Box 26)
- Publicity, News Articles Re: Pier Development (Box 26)
- Re-districting Maps (Box 26)
- Brooklyn Heights Historic District (Box 26)
- N.Y.C. Districting Commission (Box 26)
- Special Purpose Districts (Box 26)
- Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service (Box 26)
- News Articles Re: New Councilman Districts (Box 26)
- Petitioners Post-hearing Memorandum (Box 27)
- BHA vs. N.Y.C. Districting Commission & Board of Elections Petition (Box 27)
- BHA vs. N.Y.C. Districting Commission & Board of Elections – Verified Answer (Box 27)
- BHA vs. N.Y.C. Districting Commission Appendix of Affidavits (Box 27)
- BHA vs. N.Y.C. Districting Commission Cross motion and notice (Box 27)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Respondents Memo of Law Preliminary Statement (Box 27)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Petitioners Memo in Reply to Respondents Answer and Memo of Law (Box 27)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Respondents Affidavits (Box 27)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Petitioners Affidavits & Affirmations on Behalf of BHA (Box 27)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Petition for Judgment (Box 27)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Petitioners Post Hearing Memo (Box 27)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Stipulation and Order (Box 27)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Petitioners Order to Show Cause (Box 27)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Appendix of Pleading of Broad Channel Civic Association (Box 27)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Respondents Notice of Appeal (Box 27)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Affidavits of Joan G. McCabe and John W. Carrol, Order and Judgment (Box 27)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Affidavit in Opposition to Amicus (Box 27)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Motion to Vacate Automatic Stay (Box 28)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Affirmation in Opposition to P & R Motion to Vacate (Box 28)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Memorandum of P & R in Response to Motion of McCabe to Appear as Amicus (Box 28)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Affidavit in Oppostition to McCabe's Amicus (Box 28)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Appellant's Brief (Box 28)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Brief for Petitioners - Respondents (Box 28)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Appellant's Reply Brief (Box 28)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Opinion and Order (Box 28)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Notice of Appeal (Box 28)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Permission to Submit Amicus Brief (Box 28)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Amicus Brief for Joan McCabe (Box 29)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Brief for Petitioners – Respondents (Box 29)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Petitioners Reply to Respondents Answer & Memo of Law (Box 29)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Appellant's Reply Brief & Opinion (Box 29)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Record of Appeal (Vol I of II) (Box 29)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Record of Appeal (Vol II) pt. 1 (Box 29)
- BHA vs. Macchiarola, et al. Record of Appeal (Vol II) pt. 2 (Box 29)
- 97 Columbia Heights Housing Corp. V. Board of Estimate & BHA: Motion to Appeal (Box 30)
- Memo in Support of Motion to Appeal (Box 30)
- Petitioners Brief (Mary Kallas) (Box 30)
- Respondents Memo of Law (Mary Kallas) (Box 30)
- Residents Memo, Brief, & Reply Brief (Box 30)
- Respondents Affirmation in Opposition to Motion to Appeal (Box 30)
- Petitioners Memo of Law (Box 30)
- Correspondence re. 97 Columbia Heights (Box 30)
- BHA Statements in Opposition to High Rise Building (Box 30)
- Notice of Settlement (Box 30)
- 97 Columbia Heights V. Board of Estimate – Comments and Arguments (Box 30)
- Respondents Notice of Appeal (Box 30)
- Affidavit in Support to File Amicus Brief (John M. Hinchcliff) (Box 30)
- Respondents Brief for Judgment CPLR art. 78 (Box 30)
- Respondents Memo in Opposition to art. 78 Petition (Box 30)
- Respondents Reply Memo (Box 30)
- BHA Comments & Arguments Pursuant to Court of Appeals Rule 500.4f (Box 31)
- Amicus brief of N.Y. Landmarks Conservancy in Support of Appeal (Box 31)
- Respondents Verified Answer (Box 31)
- Correspondence, News Clippings, re. Judgment Pursuant to CPLR Article 78 (Box 31)
- North Heights Preservation Association V. N.Y.C. Landmarks Preservation Commission (Box 31)
- 222 Columbia Heights (Box 31)
- Hicks Street Properties (Box 31)
- BHA Miscellaneous (Box 31)
- Board of Governors, 1980-1981 (Box 31)
- Resolution for the Construction of a Second Extension at 20 Schermerhorn Street (Box 31)
- Board of Governors, 1982 (Box 31)
- BHA Garden Place Potholes (Box 31)
- BHA Montague Hotel (Box 31)
- BHA Margaret Hotel, 1981-1982 (Box 32)
- BHA Margaret Hotel, 1983-1989 (Box 32)
- Land Use Matters, 97 Columbia Heights Variance Filed with Board of Standards and Appeals, 1965-1981 (Box 32)
- Land Use Matters, 97 Columbia Heights Variance Filed with Board of Standards and Appeals, 1983-1989 (Box 32)
- BHA Opposition to Variance – 97 Columbia Heights, Jan. 1982- Jan. 1983 (Box 32)
- BHA Opposition to Variance Application 97 Columbia Heights, May 1983- June 1983 (Box 33)
- BHA Opposition to Variance Application 97 Columbia Heights, June 1983 (Box 33)
- BHA Opposition to Variance Application 97 Columbia Heights, July-Nov. 1983 (Box 33)
- BHA Opposition to Variance Application– 97 Columbia Heights, 1984 (Box 33)
- BHA 97 Columbia Heights Contributions (Box 33)
- BHA Appeal to Variance Ruling (Box 33)
- BHA Appeal Brief of BHA and Amicus (Box 33)
- BHA Brief of Petitioner-Respondent and Reply Memo (Box 33)
- BHA Margaret Hotel Renovation Planned (Box 33)
- 97 Columbia Heights – Board of Estimate (Box 35)
- Block 219 (97 Columbia Heights) Former Margaret Hotel (Box 35)
- Land Use Matters (97 Columbia Heights) (Box 35)
- 97 Columbia Heights (Box 35)
- BHA Hotel Margaret Litigation, 1980-1983 (Box 35)
- BHA Hotel Margaret Litigation, 1984-1985 (Box 35)
- 84th Precinct Records (Box 36)
- C.O.P. (Civilian Observation Patrol) Flyer (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Correspondence I (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Correspondence II (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Vouchers, Nov. 1984-Aug. 1987 (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Vouchers, Oct. 1987-Sept. 1989 (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Community Problem Reports (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Miscellaneous (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Division of Criminal Justice Services Grant, 1987-1988 (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Division of Criminal Justice Services Grant, 1989-1990 (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Car Insurance Documents (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Car Information (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Newsletter (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Private Security Guards (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Inventory of Equipment (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Letters to Division of Criminal Justice Services (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Radio Information (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Car Radio Log (Box 36)
- Paid Bills Not Vouchered, 1992-1995 (Box 36)
- Paid Bills Not Vouchered, 1991 (Box 36)
- Paid Bills Not Vouchered, 1989 (Box 36)
- Paid Bills Not Vouchered, 1982-1986 (Box 36)
- Press Clippings, Publicity and Releases (Box 36)
- Prudential Awards to C.O.P (Box 36)
- Radio and Patrol Car Bids – Radio Information (Box 36)
- Vouchers with Paid Bills I, 1989-1993 (Box 36)
- Vouchers with Paid Bills II, 1989-1993 (Box 36)
- Vouchers with Paid Bills III, 1989-1993 (Box 36)
- Vouchers with Paid Bills IV (Box 36)
- Contracts and Correspondence I, 1984-1986 (Box 36)
- Contracts and Correspondence II, 1984-1986 (Box 36)
- Contracts and Correspondence I, 1987-1989 (Box 36)
- Contracts and Correspondence II, 1987-1989 (Box 36)
- Possible Grants (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Logs and Schedules, 1992 (Box 36)
- C.O.P. Logs and Schedules, 1991 (Box 37)
- C.O.P. Logs and Schedules, July-December 1990 (Box 37)
- C.O.P. Logs and Schedules, January-June 1990 (Box 37)
- C.O.P. Logs and Schedules, July-December 1989 (Box 37)
- BHA Correspondence (Box 37)
- BHA Correspondence with Division of Criminal Justice Services (Box 37)
- BHA Safety Task Force (Box 37)
- BHA C.O.P. Quarterly Reports, 1985-1992 (Box 38)
- BHA C.O.P. Quarterly Report Forms (Box 38)
- BHA C.O.P. Report and Voucher Forms (Box 38)
- BHA C.O.P. Vouchers for Paid Bills, 1989-1993 (Box 38)
- BHA C.O.P. Contracts and Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 38)
- BHA Crime Surveys – Clark Street Association (Box 39)
- BHA Crime Surveys 1-149 (Box 39)
- BHA Crime Surveys 150-228 (Box 39)
- BHA Crime Surveys 230-350 (Box 39)
- BHA Crime Surveys 351-439 (Box 39)
- BHA Crime Surveys 440-549 (Box 39)
- BHA Crime Surveys 550-657 (Box 39)
- BHA Crime Surveys 658-704 (Box 39)
- BHA Crime Prevention Materials (Box 40)
- BHA Safe Haven Maps (Box 40)
- BHA Training – C.O.P. and Block Watchers (Box 40)
- BHA Safety Awareness Day (Box 40)
- BHA Training – Amber Light Application (Box 40)
- Monroe Place Courthouse Expansion, 1988 (Box 40)
- Monroe Place Courthouse Expansion, 1989-1990 (Box 40)
- Monroe Place Courthouse Expansion, 1991-1994 (Box 40)
- Mending Constitution – 5th Department Appellate Division of Supreme Court (Box 40)
- Criminal Court Plan (Box 40)
- BHA Miscellaneous (Box 40)
- BHA Watchtower – Proposal Draft Environmental Impact Statement I (Box 41)
- BHA Watchtower – Proposal Draft Environmental Impact Statement II (Box 41)
- BHA Watchtower – Proposed Rezoning of Blocks 204 and 208 I (Box 41)
- BHA Watchtower – Proposed Rezoning of Blocks 204 and 208 II (Box 41)
- BHA Watchtower – Environmental Statement Appendices I (Box 42)
- BHA Watchtower – Environmental Statement Appendices II (Box 42)
- BHA Watchtower – Initial Application for Amendment of Zoning Map (Box 42)
- BHA Watchtower – BHA Opposition to Zoning Changes (Box 42)
- BHA Verrazano Bridge Tolls (Box 43)
- BHA Verrazano Bridge Tolls-Opposition Faxes (Box 43)
- BHA Letters to & from Residents, 1990-1993 (Box 43)
- BHA Letters to and from Residents, 1983-1989 (Box 43)
- BHA Verrazano Bridge – Tolls – Newspaper Clippings, 1993 (Box 43)
- BHA Verrazano Bridge – Tolls – Newspaper Clippings, 1992 (Box 43)
- BHA Verrazano Bridge – Impact of One Way Tolls Technical Analysis (Box 43)
- BHA BQE Task Force (Box 44)
- BHA BQE Newspaper Clippings (Box 44)
- BHA – BQE Survey – Vibration Issue (Box 44)
- BHA – Letters from Officials, 1986-1989 (Box 44)
- BHA – Letters from Officials, 1990-1992 (Box 44)
- BHA BQE Letters to Officials from BHA, 1988-2002 (Box 44)
- BHA Polytechnic Proposal – Vibration Study (Box 44)
- BHA Hotel St. George Lawsuit Complaint (Box 45)
- BHA Hotel St. George Lawsuit Newspaper Clippings (Box 45)
- BHA Hotel St. George Lawsuit Correspondence and Clippings (Box 45)
- BHA Hotel St. George Lawsuit Briefs and Other Documents (Box 45)
- BHA Hotel St. George Lawsuit Notice of Removal andg Other Documents (Box 45)
- BHA Hotel St. George Lawsuit Defendants Affidavits and Memos in Support I (Box 45)
- BHA Hotel St. George Lawsuit Defendants Affidavits and Memos in Support II (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Correspondence (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling City Grant Application (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Contributions Received (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Cowles Trust Proposal (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Donating to New York City (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Documents (Originals) (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Fund Raising Event, April 1988 (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Marisol Escobar, Sculptor (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Monument Artists (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Monument Project BACA Grant Application (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Monument Project Fund Raising (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Monument General (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Monument Grant Application NEA (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling October Roebling Event (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Press Release (Box 45)
- BHA Roebling Project Corporate Fund Raising (Box 45)
- Cash Books: (Box 46)
- 1922-1926 (Box 46)
- 1926-1932 (Box 46)
- 1932-1940 (Box 46)
- Check Book: (Box 46)
- 1922-1938 (Box 46)
- 1923-1925 (Box 46)
- 1925-1927 (Box 46)
- 1932-1947 (Box 46)
- 1937-1956 (Box 46)
- Ledgers: (Box 46)
- 1923-1940 (Box 46)
- 1940-1949 (Box 46)
- 1954-1959 (Box 46)
- 1956-1963 (Box 46)
- 1963-1966 (Box 46)
- 1966-1971 (Box 46)
- 1971-1978 (Box 46)
- 1978-1981 (Box 46)
- 1981-1982 (Box 46)
- Cash Receipts and Disbursements: (Box 46)
- 1957-1961 (Box 46)
- Remsen Street Committee Checkbook, 1921 (Box 47)
- Ledgers: (Box 47)
- 1953 1957 (Box 47)
- 1961-1973 (Box 47)
- 1973-1980 (Box 47)